This is the time known as the Great Pirate Era.
A countless array of pirates go to battle across the seas in search of the One Piece,
the legendary treasure left behind by Gold Roger, King of the Pirates.
Monkey D. Luffy, a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit,
set sail to become the next King of the Pirates.
As Luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles,
they capture the unwanted attention of the world government,
which will use any means necessary to stop them.
Now this is exciting!
Can't wait to see what kind of adventure's up next!
With a charted course awash in danger and intrigue,
the crew will cut a path across the Grand Line to the New World.
The Battle of Marineford ended with a Navy victory.
Unable to save Ace's life, the injured Luffy was taken to Amazon Lily,
where he fell into despair.
But this is a story from another time.
Ten years ago, in the East Blue,
the brothers ran wild with dreams of a world full of adventure,
as well as the pirate flags they would someday fly.
Tucked away in Mount Corvo, living with the Bandit Dedan,
they spent their days with their other brother, Sabo.
Leaving the Dedan family for good?
The kids hideout has been built!
So how's your day been?
What more? I dug a hole right in front of our door!
When I get out, I'm gonna strangle you!
The three kids did it.
They said it was to catch some wild boars.
This is my house!
Also, tell me sooner next time, bunch of dolts!
Those brats are in for it now!
Sabo, you know damn well this is our turf
and you've got no right to be here!
Your turf.
You losers sure are delusional.
But let's skip the chit-chat and get straight to the ass-kicking!
You cocky little twerk!
It's Ace!
Don't ignore me!
Damn it!
You're dead!
That is not normal!
Oh, now you show up.
Come on, Luffy!
Hey, get up here, stupid! Hurry!
Finally!
Let's try to get a deer for dinner.
Sweet!
Well, don't just stand there!
Let's go, honey!
Luffy, wait up!
Ta-da, we're home!
Don't bother coming back next time, you brats!
We brought back dinner.
You better start cooking it now, though.
Uh-huh, cause I'm super hungry!
Hello!
I'm's guarding yourenter!
You're eager to come, can you have a game over here?
I see your
パiroot!
You're up.
Whoa!
Ah!
Whoa! Quit throwing your dinner around, you'll waste it!
He's gonna eat me!
And don't come out until you dumbasses are clean!
Hey man, quit the hat! How do you like it?
Honestly, how come we gotta do a major reclean on this place after every single dinner?
I can catch my own damn food. Those little monkeys have gotta go.
Now that ain't half bad.
Luffy, come here!
Uh, sorry boss.
Peace at last.
The end of the day is the only time I can relax.
Let's train a little more before bed.
I won't lose this time!
You're dreaming already.
And go!
Gah!
Oh, hello fairy!
Oh!
Hey Luffy, are you still alive?
Your floor sure is crummy.
You're a couple of cheaters!
Gah!
Bedtime?
I think so.
That was officially the last straw.
If we don't throw those brats out now, they'll bring down our whole operation.
Not to mention they're starting to become hazardous to my health.
There, there boss.
Take it easy.
I think they've actually been running the show for a while now.
Then I'll remind them this is the Jadon family, not the Brat family!
In other words, they're out of here!
Garp can suck it!
He doesn't own me!
Hey!
Gah?
Forgive me!
I didn't mean anything I just said!
I lost my mind!
Sorry to trouble you, but we're looking for a boy named Luffy.
We were told he lives here now.
Huh?
Lucky no!
Lucky!
You're so big and strong now.
It's been six months, so we decided to stop by and see how you're doing.
Hey, Mr. Mayor!
Just don't tell Garp, okay?
So, he's really got you sacked up here with the mountain bandits, huh?
You got a problem with that?
Of course I do!
Especially the mountain bandit part, you ruffian!
Wait, ruffian?
Is everybody from Windmill Village as annoying as you?
I brought presents for you!
Knowing Garp, he probably didn't leave you with a darn thing, did he?
Ta-da!
Bet you could use some new clothes!
That shirt's awesome!
I brought some for your friends, too.
I'd have to adjust the length, though.
Can you boys come here for a second?
Please?
Huh?
Sabo?
And you, too!
I heard this Ace Kid was pretty naughty, but you seem like a good boy!
Who the hell told you that?
That little dork!
Ace, you're blushing!
Hey, shut up!
Come on, now!
Hold still!
You're both gonna get it later.
I hope everything tastes good!
Aw, man!
I want to eat good food like this when I'm out at sea, too!
Soon as I get my pirate crew together, the first thing I'll do is find the best cook in the world!
I'm glad I'm gonna become a pirate and recruit the best cook before you do!
Yeah, you wish!
I'm gonna be a pirate before either of you don't!
You little bastards are still spouting that pirate craft?
You're both gonna be Marines someday, even if I gotta beat some dignity into you!
Ta-da!
Yes, Garpsir!
Why did you have to hit me, too?
Me, too!
Cause you're doing a crappy job of teaching my boys, clearly!
Wait, that guy is Garp?
Didn't know Ace and Luffy's grandpa was so cranky.
Hey, Squirt.
I heard you spouting some of that pirate nonsense, too.
He's not a Squirt!
He's Saba!
We already made a promise over a cup of sake, so we're gonna be pirates someday whether you like it or not!
Doesn't he ever shut up?
Really?
Well, I'm a Marine, so if you boys wanna act like a bunch of criminals, then I'll tan your hides like a bunch of criminals!
Better start running!
Hang in there, Luffy.
I think he'll do just fine, now that he has two brothers to run around with.
Oh, no you don't!
Hey, kids!
How about one of these?
I think Grandpa might be a monster!
That's enough for today.
Get some sleep so you'll be ready for tomorrow's lesson.
Cause it's gonna be even tougher.
If we don't get the heck out of here, the old man is probably gonna kill us!
And even if we do survive tomorrow, he's not gonna stop pounding us like that till we've all given up on our dream!
But I don't wanna die!
We only have one choice.
It's time for us to grow up.
Are you with me?
We will stand on our feet.
They left us this note!
What now?
Those numbskulls think they're clever.
That's your reaction?
They may only be children, but they've made enemies with every stinking crook in the city!
I mean, I don't like looking after them, but if we don't, there's no telling what could happen if someone catches them off guard.
Anyway, back to work.
Be sure to turn them into full-fledged marines by the time I get back!
There's not a chance in hell!
What'd you say?
Nothing!
Bye!
How are bandits supposed to raise a marine?
Moron!
If it's so damn easy, why don't you try?
Now, now, calm down.
You were just saying you wanted those brats out of the house.
Don't tell me you're actually worrying about them now.
What do I care?
Ha!
I'll finally be able to sleep at night, and come to think of it, they even left on their own, so it's all their fault!
Let them get murdered out there!
Alright!
We got away!
And no one followed us.
That's kinda weird.
The devil's children have the devil's luck.
How about that?
Cause Ace is the devil's son for sure.
Ah, whatever.
The Don's wanted me gone for ages.
I bet she's pretty happy right now.
Good grief!
It's coming down hard today.
Let's stay here till the rain stops.
No dumb grown-ups to tell us what to do.
That's it!
I changed my mind.
I get enough crap from Garp as is.
What are you waiting for?
Get out there and find those brats!
Yes, ma'am. Right away.
Right away.
I left my wind.
I left my room and see youTO This side.
Love IFTD
I did nothing much.
Let's see you too, too.
I thought of this.
Let's take it to the former centered꾼!
Try Dankejoe and I'm home.
Alright, thank you!
Thanks everyone for watching us.
You're welcome.
cooESS
.
Hey, guys!
Ace!
Sabo!
Luffy!
Look at this.
Cool, what is it?
I designed a hideout for us.
Until we've got our pirate ship, it sure beats sleeping outdoors every night.
And this tree should be perfect.
We can build it right here.
Our own hideout?
That's so awesome!
What do you think we should build it with?
We live right next to a mountain of trash, remember?
Now let's go.
We hold it under a pool of trash, remember?
What do you think we should build it?
We've got a lot of garbage in our house and maybe we ought to backtrack.
And we suck.
We art into Hebdo for you.
We need something else.
We do not have to live in the house.
We want a beautiful message.
Remember, we wonder if ц
Thank you.
It's different seeing them from up here.
This is nice.
Nice.
You're right.
Got a tailwind coming.
Set the sail.
Aye-aye!
Ha-ha!
That's the spot on the treasure map.
Got an enemy off the bow and starboard.
It's Blue Jam's ship.
Prepare for battle.
Damn it.
They're firing at us already.
Take evasive action now.
Hey, Luffy.
Hard aboard and make it snappy.
Roger.
Hard aboard.
No, no, no.
You forgot to say steady when you're steering the ship.
Nope, Rob.
Again.
Hard aboard and quickly.
Okay.
Hard aboard.
Steady and go!
Whoa!
It's gonna be close quarters.
Get ready, men.
We'll jump them after they come aboard.
You got it.
Let's try not to cry this time, okay?
Okay!
Ah!
Blue Jam is defeated!
All right!
That'll teach him.
Now this is how you live.
Uh-huh.
No kidding.
What an awesome ride out!
So that's where they are.
What do you mean you haven't found them yet?
Sorry.
We've talked to people who saw them at Great Terminal and in the jungle, but it's still no use.
Nobody's seen them lately.
That's impossible!
It's been two weeks!
What if that tiger ate them for dinner and there's nothing left but both?
We found them, boss!
Yeah, we found them!
Are they still alive?
Yeah, they built their own hideout deep in the jungle in that gigantic tree.
It's true.
We could even take you to sea if you like.
Thank goodness.
We're really happy for you, boss.
And to think you were worrying so much.
So they're still alive?
Well, fancy that!
I stopped caring since I was sure they'd been eaten by now.
What?
What the hell is it?
Quit standing around gawking!
You'll kill something for dinner before I decide to kill you first!
Yes, ma'am!
Police!
Double!
Wait up!
They're monsters when they're awake, but they're adorable when they're sleeping!
Oh no, dear!
You're going to catch a cold!
Please, Zabu, wait up.
They're monsters when they're awake, but they're adorable when they're sleeping.
Oh no, dear. You're going to catch a cold.
Okay, nine hours aim sure toMOire's.
Thank you.
Hm, yeah, thank you.
Here, Jack, oh yeah, there's the night of everything!
We'll have toalie the car quarterback's caritto.
Oh, hey, a trap just went off.
We've got intruders already?
Nothing?
Guess it was a fluke.
I kind of made it in a hurry, so maybe I goofed up somewhere.
I'll just check it tomorrow.
What is it?
Ouch!
Little rats.
Go ahead and be pirates.
I don't give a damn.
In fact, I hope all three of you drown at sea.
When Luffy and his friends have a dangerous encounter with a wild bear,
a strange old man comes to their rescue.
Despite his appearance, he claims to have once challenged Gold Roger.
Eyes wide with wonder, Luffy is eager to hear an untold tale of the King of the Pirates.
On the next One Piece, Luffy becoming an apprentice?
A man who fought against the King of the Pirates.
I'm going to be King of the Pirates!